翻譯: 奇跡 Jamie 不賣萌斯基
Graham 你能先把那放一邊 整理下桌子嗎
Graham, would you put that thing away and set the table?
校對: 不賣萌斯基
我正比賽呢
I'm in the middle of a race.
- 你開車的時候我煩過你嗎 - 一直在煩
- Do I bother you when you're driving? - Constantly.
前幾天 開車的時候你伸手擋我眼睛了
The other day, you put your hands over my eyes.
后期: UU123
自從Mike回去工作 下午時光就特別難熬
Since Mike's been back at work, afternoons have been crazy.
我得照看Graham 評卷子 做晚飯
I have to watch Graham, grade papers, and make dinner...
壓制: B B
每周二 周四 還有周六輪班
Tuesdays, Thursdays, and alternate Saturdays.
- 我買了泰國菜 該死 - 是周二 周六
- I got Thai food. Damn it. - Oh, it was Tuesdays, Saturdays,
- 周四輪班 - 我們有書面協議的
- and alternate Thursdays. - It worked on paper.
不過我們弄丟了
We just lost the paper.
沒事啊 不錯啊 披薩和泰國菜
Oh, no, no, it's great. Pizza and Thai food.
這兩樣從沒組合過真奇了
There's probably no reason those two have never been combined.
不得不提醒你下啊
You know, I don't wanna alarm you,
我們兒子已經變成僵尸
but our son has become a zombie.
我必須給他游戲機 讓他別煩我
I had to give him that game earlier to keep him off of me.
你不在場 你不知道那是什么情況
You weren't there. You don't know what it was like, man.
你是在說Graham還是越南啊
Are you talking about Graham or Vietnam?
在說美國因國內反戰浪潮退出越戰導致戰敗
我們要恢復秩序 Mike 首要工作就是
We need to restore order, Mike, and the first job needs to be
給Graham找個新的課外活動
getting Graham into a new after-school activity.
Chelsea Piers要開一個曲棍球課
Chelsea Piers is starting a hockey program.
- 送他到那里去 - 曲棍球
- We could sign him up for that. - Hockey?
你只是因為你喜歡曲棍球才讓他去學
You just want him to do hockey because you like hockey.
不 我讓他學曲棍球是我覺得他有天賦
No, I want him to do hockey 'cause I think he'd be good at it.
你真想讓他整天被一群壯漢拳打腳踢嗎
Do you really want him getting roughed up by a bunch of thugs?
我是說 他這么有創造力
I mean, he's such a creative kid.
可能 陶藝不錯
I was thinking maybe... pottery.
這妥妥不會被壯漢揍了
Oh, that'll keep him safe from the thugs.
陶藝很不錯啊 弄臟你的手
Oh, pottery is so great. You get your hands dirty.
在轉盤上擺弄你的陶土
You're workin' the earth on your wheel.
憂慮就這么消散了
You're just spinnin' your cares away.
Annie看了太多<人鬼情未了>了
Annie has seen the movie Ghost too many times.
說個比這更性感的陶藝電影場景 你說
Okay, name a sexier pottery scene, I dare you.
除了這還有啥陶藝電影場景
Name any other pottery scene.
我只是想怎么也該讓一個孩子搞搞運動
Look, I just think we should have one kid who's athletic.
我是說 我們已經錯過Eve和Ian了
I mean, we let Eve and Ian slip through our fingers.
- 他倆太差了 - Ian沒那么差
- They're a couple of duds. - Ian's not so bad.
是嗎 瞧好了 兒子 小心
Oh, yeah? Watch this. Hey, son, heads up.
爸 那可是佛羅里達的臍橙
Whoa! Dad! That is a Florida navel.
你想什么呢
Have you lost your damn mind?
好吧 至少他知道產地
Well, at least he knows its produce.
好吧 我們現在沒必要操心Graham吧
All right, we don't have to worry about Graham right now, okay?
也許我們能找個第三方案 我們都喜歡的
Maybe we will find a third thing that we both like.
第三方案 我喜歡
Third thing. I like that.
現在 我們吃晚飯吧 還有第二頓晚飯
In the meantime, let's have dinner... and other dinner.
誰想來點油炸玉米粉餅 該死
Who wants quesadillas? Damn it.
以及第三頓晚餐
And the other dinner...
又 見 彩 虹
第一季  第四集
電波誠譯
瞧瞧 我們碰都沒碰油炸玉米粉餅
Look at that, we didn't even touch the quesadillas.
因此 理論上這還是歸我所有
And since they're technically still my property...
嘿 我手機上沒裝推特啊
Oh, hey, I don't have Twitter on my phone.
- 不 那是我手機 - 咱倆的殼一樣啊
- No, that's my phone. - We have the same cases?
同款殼哦
Twinsies.
單向樂隊多棒啊
How awesome is one direction?
- 我用那殼是為了搞笑 - 在蹩腳方面
- Oh, mine's ironic. - At being lame?
你有消息提醒
Oh, hey, you got a tweet,
說的不是什么好話 誰是"我98年去過那"
and it is not nice. Who is "Iwentthere98"?
是 Lisa Mitchell
It's Lisa Mitchell.
她是學校里特討厭一姑娘
She's this horrible girl from school.
她在推特上跟我開戰只是因為我說了
She started a Twitter war with me all because I said
- 我喜歡她的媽媽牛仔褲 - 媽媽牛仔褲
- I liked her mom jeans. - Mom jeans.
超遜 這算是媽媽牛仔褲嗎
Lame. Are these mom jeans?
事實上 我其實挺喜歡這褲子
The thing is, I actually liked them.
人們從前掩飾船只
They used to camouflage ships
讓大家難以區分是要入港還是出港
so you couldn't tell if they were coming or going.
coming or going 雙關為"青春期體型變形還是年齡到了體型不再"= =
- 那褲子就那用處 - 這話你該發給她
- Those pants were like that. - Well, you should tweet that,
或者一些聽起來不像個船癡的話
or something where you don't sound like a boat nerd.
給 給我那玩意兒
Here gi... gi... give me that thing.
我來告訴你怎么做
Let me show you how this is done.
- 偷懶啊 - 不 不 我是
- Hardly working? - Oh, no, I'm... I'm...
在做一條"為什么曲棍球比陶藝好"的新聞
I'm researching a piece about how hockey is better than pottery.
我們是說過要取材廣泛
We talked about broad appeal,
但是 Mike 你這也太廣了吧
Mike, but, damn, you swimmin' away from shore.
好吧 跟你說實話
Okay, to tell you the truth,
我打算讓Graham學曲棍球
I'm tryin' to get Graham into hockey,
Annie卻強烈要求學陶藝
and Annie's pushing for pottery.
我小表弟去學了陶藝 一年以后
My little cousin got into pottery. A year later,
- 在墨西哥發現他的尸體 - 我就這意思啊
- they found him dead in Mexico. - That's what I'm saying.
好吧 也不太是我的意思
Well, that's not exactly what I'm saying,
不過我會留它做我的后備論據
but I'll keep that argument in my back pocket.
我一直想跟你談談主播職位的事
Hey, I've been meaning to talk to you about the anchor position.
Harris 我接下這工作時就告訴過你
Harris, I told you when I took this job,
我對主播沒興趣
I-I'm not interested in anchor.
我就想做個兼職通訊員
I'm... I'm just happy being a part-time correspondent.
- 是這樣 但... - 盡管很榮幸
- Right, and... - Although I'm flattered
你考慮過我 但是 我不是為了想
that you thought of me, and I'm not just saying that
多抬抬價碼才這么說的
because I'm holding out for more money.
不過 你有既定價碼嗎 常理來說都有的
Although, is there a number? There's always a number.
Mike 我沒在給你提供職位
Hey, I'm not offering you the gig, Mike.
- 我需要你當記者 - 誰說我想要那個職位
- I need you as a reporter. - Who said I wanted the gig?
我想告訴你我要雇用Susan Rodriguez Jones
I'm trying to tell you that I'm hiring Susan Rodriguez Jones.
- Susan Jones - 嗯
- Suzy Jones? - Mm-hmm.
她就是個女魔頭啊
She's a devil woman.
Susan Jones是我在奧蘭多時的現場制片
Suzy Jones was my field producer in Orlando.
有次 我擱淺在沼澤地里她就把我丟那了
One day, she left me stranded in the Everglades
然后不小心用了我的汽船替我報道了新聞
when she "Accidentally" Took my airboat to cover my story.
不是她找到了你嗎
But wasn't she the one who found you?
17個小時 她做完指甲之后
17 hours later, after she did her nails.
她把營救我的事件寫進全國新聞讓她自己
She turned my rescue into a national story to...
- 事業飛黃騰達 - Mike 你是個正直的男人
- to push her own career. - Aw, Mike, you're a man of integrity,
但每次說起沼澤事件
but when you start talking about that swamp,
就成了個喋喋不休的瘋子
you sound straight-up cuckoo bananas.
我徒手殺了一條水蛇啊
I killed a water moccasin with my bare hands.
喔 Michael Henry
Oh! Michael Henry.
- Suzy Jones - Suzy Rodriguez-Jones
- Suzy Jones. - Suzy Rodriguez-Jones.
哦 天啊 你看起來都沒老
Oh, gosh, you haven't aged a day.
你跟惡魔簽契約了嗎
What, did you make a deal with the devil?
你說說看啊
You tell me.
Harris 我還沒正式報到
Hey, Harris. I'm not officially here.
我只是來看看我桌子到了沒
I'm just overseeing the delivery of my desk.
我希望你不會太別扭
I hope this isn't too weird for you.
我是說 以前我只是個實習生
I mean, the fact that I used to be the intern,
現在 我搬進拐角辦公室了
and now I'm... I'm moving into the corner office,
拐角處的辦公室通常是級別高的人所有
還有一個大桃木桌子
and I've got the big, mahogany desk
- Walter Cronkite送給我的 - 送給你
- that Walter Cronkite gave to me. - Gave to you?
60年代到80年代初CBS傳奇主播 報道過多起重大歷史事件
我倒想聽聽Walter怎么說的
I'd like to hear Walter's side of the story.
不過我們肯定問不到了 這謊撒的妙啊
Although we never will. How convenient.
你大概可以蜷縮在
Hey, you could probably curl
其中一個抽屜里 小憩一會
up in one of the drawers, take a little nap.
開玩笑啦 那明天見 伙計們
I'm kidding. Hey, I'll see you tomorrow, guys.
看到了嗎
Did you see that?
我看見你暗指她謀殺了Walter Cronkite
Yeah, I saw you implying that she killed Walter Cronkite.
17個小時困在沼澤地里 Harris
17 hours in the glades, Harris.
我喝了滿滿一樂福鞋的沼澤水
I drank a loafer full of swamp water.
- 里面還有蝌蚪 - 蝌蚪
- There were tadpoles in there. - A tadpole?
的確有東西在里面扭來扭去嘛
Something was wiggling around in there.
聽著 細節不重要
Look, the details aren't important.
重點是她故意留我在那里
What's important is she left me on purpose.
- 你必須相信我 - 我相信你
- You gotta believe me. - I believe you.
你是真的相信我
Do you believe me "Believe me"?
還是只是看在情分上相信我
Or do you just believe me out of loyalty?
別傷害你自己了
Don't pick at the scab.
我們得另尋方法了
We need a better system.
工作一團糟 家庭生活一團糟
Work was a mess. Home life was a mess.
我真的需要贏一次
I just really needed a win.
邊走路邊玩游戲 你是動物啊
Walking while playing a video game. Wow. You're an animal.
這種手眼協調能力
That's the kind of hand-eye coordination
天生就是曲棍球運動員的料子
that makes for a natural-born hockey player.
- 真的嗎 - 大概吧
- Really? - Sort of.
既然你提起了曲棍球這話題
Hey, since you brought up hockey,
幫你報個曲棍球兒童班怎樣
what do you say we sign you up for a youth league?
- 好啊 - 好極了
- Okay. - Great.
跟你媽說這是你自己的主意
And tell mom it was your idea.
只要不是周二的課就行
As long as it's not on Tuesdays.
- 我周二要上陶藝課 - 什么
- That's when I have pottery class. - What?
媽說那是我的主意
Mom says it was my idea.
陶藝課嗎 說好的第三種方案呢
Pottery? What happened to the third thing?
我知道 我也一直覺得很愧疚
I know, I'm sorry, and I was feeling so bad about it
- 直到找到了這個 - 其實那是我的
- until I found this. - Well, that's actually my helmet, so...
是嗎 這是你為多年沒碰的運動
Oh, okay, it's your brand-new, tiny helmet
新買的迷你頭盔嗎
for a sport you haven't played in years.
那我錯了 那戴起來看看吧
My bad. Let's see it on you, just for fun.
我知道戴起來會挺有趣的
Well, I-I can see how that would be fun, but...
可我今天做了播報新聞造型
but I-I have news hair right now.
- 如果能戴上 我就不怪你 - 好吧
- If the helmet fits, I must acquit. - Fine.
如果你想道歉 幾時都可以
So any time you feel like apologizing...
好吧 我給他買了這頭盔
Fine. I bought him the helmet
怕他突然想玩玩曲棍球才買的
on the off chance that he might wanna play hockey.
可你幫他報了課程 直接報了
But you enrolled him. Enrolled.
我不得不啊 陶藝課快報滿了
I had to, the pottery class was filling up.
- 這怎么可能 - 反正米已成炊了
- There's no way that's true. - What's done is done.
就當作我眼明手快 而你錯失良機了
Let's just chalk it up to "You snooze, you lose."
還沒完 我要給Graham報個曲棍球班
Better yet, why don't I sign Graham up for hockey, he does
他兩個都上 然后自己選更喜歡哪個
both, and we let him decide for himself which one he likes best?
贊成 看他自己喜歡哪個誰就贏
Okay, you're on. Best hobby wins.
親愛的 這事關Graham
Honey, this is about Graham.
- 可不是個比賽 - 抱歉
- It's not a competition. - I'm sorry.
若是個比賽 肯定完虐你
If it were a competition, I'd crush you.
嘿 爸 小心
Hey, dad, heads up.
如果是個西柚 我們肯定被砸死了
If that were a grapefruit, we'd be dead by now.
這比陶藝工作服酷多了 是吧
It's a lot better than that pottery smock, isn't it?
趕緊聞聞這個 以后就臭氣熏天了
Smell this, that's the best it's ever gonna smell.
我動不了 就像是變成一個大塊頭
I can't move. It's like I'm wearing another guy.
慢慢會習慣的
Aw, you'll get used to it.
等到你第一個大力射門
Wait till you take your first slap shot.
很過癮的 感覺超棒
It's addicting. It's like crack,
其實那也沒什么的
which is not a thing, by the way.
Mike Henry 終于來了個懂兩下子的爹
Whoa, Mike Henry. Finally, a dad with some skills.
你能給我們幫點忙
You know, we could really use some help out here.
我是說 如果你想的話
I mean, if you're up to it.
太久沒打了 我不知道還能打得動不
Well, it's been a while. I don't know if I can still play.
進球一條龍 看見沒 Greg
Coast to coast, baby. Taste it, Greg!
事實上 我在冰面上活動得更自如
Actually, I move much better on the ice.
若是住在一個冰星球上 我大概能稱帝了
If only I lived on an ice planet, I'd... I'd be emperor.
不錯啊 守門那個是咱這最差勁的孩子
Impressive. You scored on our weakest kid.
你說過我有潛力的
You said I had potential!
Aidan 走開 孩子們 都離開冰場
Aidan, out of the net. Kids, get off the ice!
今天我們上 觀摩課
Today, we learn... by watching.
是我寫給"大都市"的文章 關于單側乳房的
It's my cosmo article, the one on side-boob.
被電腦搞丟了
The computer just lost it.
我整整一個月都在寫這個
It's the only thing I've written all month.
別擔心 電腦高手在此
Don't worry. The Doctor is in.
好嘞 打開回收站 把圖標拉回來
All right, open trash, drag icon,
- 成功破解你電腦 - Ian 你真是個天才
- and system hacked. - Ian, you're a genius.
我都有寫作陰影了
I have had this crazy case of writer's block.
我 幾乎找不到自己的心聲
I-I-I ca... I just... I can't find my voice,
而這篇文章
And this article was gonna be the thing
就是我的東山再起之作
that pulled me out of my slump.
- 太垃圾了 刪掉 - 噢
- Oh, it's garbage. Trash it. - Oh.
真是很感激你啊 Leigh姑姑
Thanks a lot, Aunt Leigh.
你幫我發的那條推文 弄巧成拙
That tweet you had me send totally backfired.
"我98年去過那"罵了我一天
Iwentthere98 has been flaming me all day.
你看吧
Check it out.
這可真夠氣的 不錯啊98
Whoa, she really went there... 98.
- 我也看 - 真是
- Let me see. - Wha...
這條犀利 這條太刻薄
Oh, good one. Mm, too mean.
這條不夠嚴謹啊
This one isn't even factually accurate.
這怎么進的去 可以嗎
That would never fit in there. Would it?
經過實踐嘛...
With practice...
她最后一條推文 還說我跑步姿勢奇怪
in her last tweet, she said that I run weird.
現在學校里人人都叫我”那個跑步踢到屁股的”
And now, everyone at school is calling me "The self-butt-kicker."
現在網上就可以隨意亂說 無論真實與否
I guess online, you can just say anything, even if it's not true.
什么 真的是這樣
Wait, it's true?
寶貝 那你覺得為什么你跑步屁股會疼呢
Sweetie, why do you think your butt hurts when you run?
- 我再也不玩推特了 - Eve 別啊
- I quit Twitter! - Eve, no.
Ian 你太糟了 應該是這樣的
Ian, that's terrible. It's like this.
你們在學Eve跑步嗎
Oh. You guys doing Eve's run?
準沒錯
Yeah.
這些松餅就是我對大家的一些心意
So these muffins are just a small way of saying
我非常高興加入NBC四臺大家庭
how happy I am to be joining the NBC4 family.
謝謝大家
So thank you.
不敢相信她還叫Susan Rodriguez-Jones
Can't believe she's still going by Susan Rodriguez-Jones.
她曾嫁給一個內衣模特六周
She married an underwear model for six weeks
- 就是為了這多元化名字 - 忍忍吧 Mike
- so she could seem more multi-culti. - Oh, suck it up, Mike.
既然Susan來了 我們都得做點犧牲
We all gotta make sacrifices now that Susan's on board.
主播才能用豪華衛生間
Anchors get the executive bathroom.
前幾周都是我的呢
That's been my go-to for weeks.
你說得對 我去說兩句歡迎詞
You're right, I'm gonna say a few words of welcome.
- 別這樣啊 - Susan 說的不錯啊
- Oh, no, no, no, no. - Susan. Nice speech.
謝謝大家 真是太感人了
Thank you. Very... very... very touching.
不得不說 沼澤事件后你長進了不少啊
Um, I wanna say you've come a long way since the 'Glades.
真高興你提起那些往事
I am so glad you brought up the old days.
我有話要聲明 各位
I need to come clean about something, everyone.
我之所以有今天的成績 完全就是因為
The whole reason I even have a career today is because...
在Mike Henry手下干活時碰上了好運氣
I had the absolute good fortune of working under Mike Henry.
幸虧我把你從沼澤救出來了
Mm, I am so glad I found you in that swamp.
這么一想
If you think about it,
我救了你 你也救了我 Mike
I had to save you so that you could save me, Mike.
我不知道該不該鼓掌
I don't know. Should I clap or not?
不
No.
是啊 你說得對 她就是個女魔頭
Yeah, you called it. She's a devil woman.
Mike 還有一件事
Oh, Mike, just one more thing.
你以為大家還會在乎沼澤事件嗎 跳梁小丑
You think anyone gives a damn about the 'Glades, ass clown?
沼澤事件已經是過去的事了 你也是
The 'Glades are a thing of the past, like you.
這是老娘的臺了 若你再惹毛我
This is my station now, and if you cross me again,
我就把你帶到 連我都找不到你的地方
I will take you some place where I will never find you,
否則我就不叫Susan Rodriguez-Jones
or my name isn't Susan Rodriguez-Jones.
本來就不叫
It isn't.
她不叫這名 你知道
It isn't, you know.
接住 Mike
Here you go, Mike.
真棒
Yes!
流汗發泄一下感覺真好
It felt good to blow off some steam.
更重要的是 這還能激勵Graham
But more importantly, it... it felt good to inspire Graham.
這叫傳接戰術
And that's called a give-and-go.
等你火候到了 這就是制勝招啊
It'll be a staple of your game when you're ice-ready.
看著我
In the meantime, eyes on me.
怎么不用泥刀呢 或者用磨邊機吧
Why don't you try the mud cutter? Or the aftosa edger?
還是試試這個鈍刀
Or how about this little pokey guy?
我覺得我更喜歡曲棍球
I think I like hockey better.
不不不 你不適合打曲棍球
No, no, no, no. No, you're not a hockey kid.
你富有創造力 像我
You're creative, like me.
如果你真的喜歡這個
If you really get into this,
我們可以把家里工藝室打掃一下 在那做
we could clear out the crafting room and actually craft in there.
要不你做給我看看吧
Maybe I'd like it more if you show me.
- 我看著學更快 - 好吧 我做做看
- I learn better by watching. - Okay, I can do that.
好的
Okay.
看著不錯哦 媽媽 我已經在學了哦
Looking good, Mom. I'm learning already.
開什么玩笑
You gotta be kidding me.
- 周二就這么猛啊 - 就是心情舒暢
- Wow, that's big for a Tuesday. - Just feelin' free.
Graham陶藝課做的嗎
Graham make that in pottery class?
是啊 出自小男孩之手
Yeah, made it with his boy hands.
我知道他才8歲 但這也太那啥了
I know he's only eight, but yikes.
是嗎 我覺得不錯啊 對任何年齡層來說
Really? I-I think it's pretty good for someone of any age.
還好他還有曲棍球 他可喜歡了
Well, at least he has hockey. He likes that.
他也喜歡陶藝啊
Oh, he's loving pottery too.
你知道嗎 他真的喜歡
You know, he's just loving it, and...
而且很有天賦 水漏出來了
it's really promising, and... it's leaking.
你們在太好了
I'm glad you guys are here.
我在練習新的跑步方式
I've been working on a new run.
你們有時間看看嗎
Do you have a second to take a look?
- 當然  - 來吧
- Sure. - Yeah.
好的
Okay.
你還能跑的更快點嗎
Are you gonna go any faster?
需要時間啊 這才一天嘛 煩人
In time. It's been a day. God!
我就在那兒 憑我一人之力
So there I am, single-handedly trying
試圖攔截一個東洛杉磯的開槍逃逸犯
to stop a drive-by shooting in east L.A.
沒一個記者
Now, no reporter wants
想要進自己的新聞報道里 對嗎
to be the subject of their own story, right?
- 但這事關人命啊 - 她在玩弄你們所有人
- But this was about saving lives. - She's playing all of you.
前幾天 她差不多承認了
You know, the other day, she practically admitted
是她把我丟沼澤那兒的
she left me stranded in the swamp.
所以呢 是在她淚眼婆裟的
Uh-huh. Was that before or after
告訴大家你是甘地之后
she tearfully told the whole office
最偉大的人之前還是之后
that you were the greatest man since Gandhi?
- 之后  - 砰
- It was after. - Bam!
那貨車向我沖來
And then the van winged me,
我被撞飛了 直直穿過一家當地
and I went down, right through the window
墨西哥快餐店的窗戶
of a local taqueria.
這就是為什么我的左手沒有知覺
And that is why I have no feeling in my left hand.
真的嗎 這故事太驚人了
Really? That's... that's an amazing story.
沒知覺 完全沒知覺嗎
No feeling? No feeling at all?
- 像死魚一樣嗎  - 對
- Just like a dead fish? - Yeah.
- 哇 - 你看
- Wow. - Oh, well, here.
- 這的確能證明  - 可不嘛
- That proves that. - Mm.
- 那我先走了  - 再見
- Guess I'll just be on my way. - Okay.
這樣痛了吧
I know... I know it hurts right now.
或許你今天就回家工作吧
Yeah, no, maybe you need to work from home today.
一個好的調查記者力氣就該這么大
Oh, no, a good investigative reporter takes big swings,
即使有著短小迷你的手
even if he has tiny, little arms.
等等 讓我再試一次
No, let me give it another shot.
每個細節都不放過 干得好 先生
No stone unturned. Nice work, sir.
- 這可了不得  - 該死的
- Look at that. - Motherfu...
- 甜心 有見到Eve嗎  - 她還在弄年鑒呢
- Hey, doll, have you seen Eve? - Oh, she's still at yearbook.
真想知道今年誰的"最美眼睛"被搶了
I wonder who's gonna get robbed for "Best eyes" This year.
我又拿錯她手機了
I grabbed her phone by mistake again.
好消息是 我讓"我98年去過那"老實了
Good news, I put iwentthere98 in her place.
沒有錯 我狠狠臭罵了她一頓
Oh, yeah. I threw her some major shade.
臟詞源源不斷的涌出腦海啊
The words just flowed from me.
或許我是有點被寫作陰影煩到了啦
So maybe I was a little frustrated from this writer's block,
又或許是向一個少女發泄出來了
and maybe I was taking it out on a teenager.
但我還有話要說 我又不認識她
But in my defense, I didn't know her.
Lisa"賤"Chell再也不會給Eve添亂子了
Lisa "Bitchell" Will not be messing with Eve anymore.
- Lisa"賤"Chell  - 本名叫Lisa Mitchell啦
- "Lisa Bitchell"? - Her real name's Lisa Mitchell.
Mitch不是和"賤"押韻嘛 我真是火力全開
"Mitch" Rhymes with "Bitch"? I can't turn it off.
我知道她本名叫什么
Oh, I know what her real name is.
Lisa Mitchell現實生活中是個惡霸
Lisa Mitchell is a real-life bully.
- 她去年還揍扁了個漢子  - 真的嗎
- She even beat up a guy last year. - Seriously?
但不能證明她揍的那個漢子怎么了
Yeah. But it doesn't say anything about the guy she beat up.
更證明了她是怎樣的一個人 Lisa賤招多
It says more about her. Lisa fights dirty.
我們得提醒Eve 我打給她
We have to warn Eve. I'll... I'll call her.
你怎么打給她 她手機在你的
How are you gonna call her? You have her phone.
該死 或許我手機在她的
Crap. Well, maybe she has my phone.
我打給我 把手機給我
I'll call me. Just give me the phone!
沒時間互相怪罪了 我們趕緊走
No time to assign blame. We have to get goin'.
快點去Eve學校 Lisa可能在語言教室門口
We have to get to Eve's school. Lisa's probably waiting outside
等著呢 給Eve喉嚨劈一掌啥的
the language lab so she can chop Eve in the throat or something.
快跑
Run!
打曲棍球可能會讓你撞掉牙
Hockey may knock your teeth out,
但陶藝打碎的是你的心
but pottery breaks your heart.
我沒權力讓
I had no right to keep
Graham參加一個他不喜歡的興趣班
Graham in an activity that he wasn't enjoying.
于是 我找到了真正給予他支持的方式
And then, I found a way to support him for real.
可憐的小家伙忘記帶冰鞋了
The poor little guy forgot his skates.
Susan的事你是對的 她的手可有活力了
Well, you're right about Susan. Her hand is very much alive,
她就是個超級大騙子
and she's a crazy, crazy liar.
終于有人信我了
- Yes, finally, someone believes me.
我們可不能默許
You know we can't have a
一個騙子坐在主播椅上
conniving liar in the anchor chair, so...
- 我沒說她要走啊  - 啥
- Oh, she's not going anywhere. - What?
她釘了她的手啊 Mike 然后忍著
She stapled her hand, Mike, and sucked up the insane
那種劇烈的痛楚長達七分鐘
amount of pain she was feeling for seven minutes.
就是要這種冷血瘋子
That's the kind of cold-blooded
才能讓我們重回巔峰
crazy that's gonna put us back on top.
她會拖垮整個臺的啊
She's gonna bring down the entire station.
聽著 誰都能釘自己的手的 看著
Look, anyone can staple their hand. I mean, look.
好的 我瞄不準我的手
Okay, I'm... I'm a moving target.
來 我抓住我的手 你來釘
Ah, here, I'll hold my hand. You staple.
- 需要兩個人  - 這瘋勁就留在沼澤地吧
- It's a two-man job. - Oh, leave it in the 'Glades, Mike.
我來幫忙 我有個釘槍
I'll help! I've got a staple gun.
我希望沒有太遲
I hope we're not too late.
她在那
There she is!
她學會怎么跑步了
She learned how to run.
她在跑呢
She's running.
但還是被逮到了
But she still got caught.
我們學校絕不容忍暴力事件
We have a zero-tolerance policy for fights at our school.
僅憑那些推文評論來說
And as far as those Twitter comments go,
- 就已經無法接受了  - 不是我寫的
- completely unacceptable. - But I didn't write them.
- 是我干的  - 什么
- I did. - What?
真抱歉 Eve 我只想幫幫你
I'm so sorry, Eve. I-I was just trying to get your back, so...
你以為我會相信那些幼稚的羞辱話語
Do you really expect me to believe that a grown woman
是出自一個成年女性之口嗎
came up with all those childish insults?
幼稚 我覺得是聰明 "大腿"Cyrus
Childish? I'd say clever. "Thigh-ly" Cyrus?
請自行聯想Miley Cyrus近期充滿性暗示的出格表演和造型
- 欲求不滿小姐  - 就是不滿
- "Little miss can't-get-dong"? - She can't.
"跟人處不好小姐"諧音
我是說 還是能的 只要她想
I mean, she could, if she wanted to.
是她自己的身體 她的樂園
It's her body. It's her wonderland.
校長說話呢 專心聽
You know, the Principal's talking, guys, focus up.
如果那些真是你寫的 那我真無比震驚
Well, if you actually did write those tweets, I am appalled.
那就震驚吧 因為全是我寫的
Well, be appalled, because I wrote all of them.
全部都是 我的天 全是我寫的
All of them! Oh, my god, I wrote all of them.
我終于聽到自己的心聲了 賤人賤語
I finally found my voice. It's bitchy teen!
- 你在這兒呢  - 嘿
- There you are. - Hey.
Graham 抱歉我逼你做陶藝了
Graham, I am so sorry that I forced you to do pottery.
顯然 你喜歡曲棍球
Clearly, you love hockey.
干嘛不上場讓我看看你有什么本事
Now, why don't you get out there and show me what you got?
我不需要這個
I don't need those.
- 啥  - 我們在上觀摩課
- What? - We learn by watching.
老爸們在打
The dads are playing.
- 老婆 - 老婆來了
- Wife! - Wife.
嘿親愛的
Hey, honey.
抱歉 Mike
Sorry, Mike.
- 我可能再也不能親人了  - 別嬌氣了
- You know, I may never kiss again. - Don't be a baby.
積極面是 那些曲棍球練習
The upside is, all that time at hockey practice
讓Graham賽車游戲越玩越好了
made Graham really good at his driving game.
這么說你別難過 陶藝課他也沒閑著
Yeah, well, don't feel bad. That's all he did at pottery too.
- 花瓶是我做的  - 昨天那個花瓶嗎
- I made that vase. - That vase from yesterday?
我超愛的那個
That vase I loved?
這個的起因就是因為我們以為Graham
You know, all this started because we thought Graham needed
需要點什么 但我想
something, but I'm starting to think,
或許是我們需要點什么
like, maybe we needed something.
你說的對 我們不能逼Graham像我們一樣
You're right, we can't force Graham to be like us.
我們得征求他自己的意見
We should ask him what he wants to do.
對 如果他說"電子游戲"
Yeah, and if he says, "Video games,"
那再叫他換個興趣就是了
We just tell him to make another choice.
話說回來那花瓶哪去了
Hey, where is that vase by the way?
漏水那個嗎 扔垃圾桶了
Oh, the leaky one? I put that in the trash.
或許它另有用處呢
I-I may have a use for it.
有時 你會想
Sometimes, it's tempting to
干涉孩子的生活甚至幫他們生活
step in and try to live your kids' lives for them.
但當你讓他們做自己時
But when you let them be themselves,
不僅對他們好
not only is it good for them,
也讓你騰出空余專注自己的生活
it frees you up to focus on yourself
處理自己的問題
and deal with your own problems.
真貼心
Aw. This is sweet.
Cronkite的桌子
Cronkite's desk!
噢 不
Oh. Oh, no. Oh.
電波字幕組 歡迎您的加入
官方網站:www.dbfansub.com
新浪微博:@電波字幕組